There are severe delays on the
Bakerloo Line. Minor delays
between Queen's Park and Harrow
and Wealdstone due to an earlier
fire alert at Kilburn High Road.
There are severe delays on the
Central Line. Severe delays
between Leytonstone and Epping
and Woodford via Hainault and
Newbury Park and MINOR DELAYS on
the rest of the line, while we
fix a signal failure at
Leytonstone. Tickets will be accepted on
London Buses, Greater Anglia via
any reasonable route and
Chiltern Railways between West
Ruislip and Marylebone.
There are minor delays on the
Central Line. Severe delays
between Leytonstone and Epping
and Woodford via Hainault and
Newbury Park and MINOR DELAYS on
the rest of the line, while we
fix a signal failure at
Leytonstone. Tickets will be accepted on
London Buses, Greater Anglia via
any reasonable route and
Chiltern Railways between West
Ruislip and Marylebone.
There are severe delays on the
District Line. Severe delays
between Wimbledon and Edgware
Road and Minor delays between
Earl's Court and Richmond /
Ealing Broadway due to an earlier
signal failure at Earl's Court,
your tickets will be accepted on
the buses.
There are minor delays on the
District Line. Severe delays
between Wimbledon and Edgware
Road and Minor delays between
Earl's Court and Richmond /
Ealing Broadway due to an earlier
signal failure at Earl's Court,
your tickets will be accepted on
the buses.
There is a partial closure on
the Metropolitan Line. Saturday
24, Sunday 25 and Bank Holiday
Monday 26 August, no service
between Rayners Lane and
Uxbridge. Replacement buses operate.
There is a partial closure on
the Piccadilly Line. Saturday 24,
Sunday 25 and Bank Holiday
Monday 26 August, no service between
Rayners Lane and Uxbridge.
Replacement buses operate.
The Waterloo & City Line is
closed. The service will resume
again at 08:00 on Monday.
There is a good service on all
other lines.